let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "The scientist most closely associated with the Theory of Evolution is? ",
    answer: "Darwin",
    options: ["Dalton", "Einstein", "Mendeleyev", "Darwin"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "All of the following are mammals except ",
    answer: "Shark",
    options: ["Whale", "Shark", "Dolphin", "Seal"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A cell wall is present only in ",
    answer: "Bacteria",
    options: ["Bacteria", "Protozoa", "Algae", "Virus"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "The substance that conducts electricity by the movement of ions is",
    answer: "Molten Sodium Chloride",
    options: ["Graphite", "Mercury", "Molten Sodium Chloride", "Molten Lead"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question:
      "Zainab is expecting her 10th child. All of her other children are females. The probability that her 10th child will also be a girl is",
    answer: "0.5",
    options: ["0.9", "0.1", "0.5", "None of these"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "The apparatus that is most suitable for accurately measuring 230 cm3 of liquid is",
    answer: "Burette",
    options: ["Burette", "Pipette", "Cylinder", "Beaker"],
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "The gas that is industrially obtained using fractional distillation is",
    answer: "Nitrogen",
    options: ["Nitrogen", "Chlorine", "Ammonia", "Hydrogen"],
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Oxidation takes places on the following electrode",
    answer: "Anode",
    options: ["Anode", "Cathode", "Both anode and cathode", "None of these"],
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The most effective means of corrosion is",
    answer: "Air",
    options: ["Air", "Water", "CO2", "N2"],
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following situations is impossible",
    answer: "A body having constant velocity but non-zero acceleration",
    options: [
      "A body having velocity East and acceleration West",
      "A body having velocity East and acceleration East",
      "A body having zero velocity but non-zero acceleration",
      "A body having constant velocity but non-zero acceleration",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question:
      "If a fixed mass of water is cooled slowly from 100C to 00C, its volume",
    answer: "First decreases and then increases",
    options: [
      "Increases steadily",
      "Decreases steadily",
      "First increases and then decreases",
      "First decreases and then increases",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question:
      "Which of the following properties of a solid would change if we were transported from the Earth to the Moon?",
    answer: "Weight",
    options: ["Mass", "Volume", "Density", "Weight"],
  },

  {
    numb: 13,
    question:
      "A moth at about eye level is 10 cm in front of a plane mirror; you are behind the moth, 30 cm from the mirror. The distance Fbetween your eyes and the apparent position of the moth's image in the mirror is",
    answer: "40 cm",
    options: ["50 cm", "30 cm", "40 cm", "60 cm"],
  },

  {
    numb: 14,
    question:
      "When two glucose (C6H12O6) molecules are combined to form a molecule of maltose (C12H22O11), the formula of the maltose molecule is not C12H24O12 because ",
    answer: "Dehydration synthesis takes place",
    options: [
      "Hydrolysis takes place",
      "Dehydration synthesis takes place",
      "Transpiration takes place",
      "Water is added",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Of the following terms, the one that includes all others is",
    answer: "Biodiversity",
    options: [
      "Species diversity",
      "Biodiversity",
      "Genetic diversity",
      "Ecosystem diversity",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Auxin serve to increase rate of",
    answer: "Growth",
    options: ["Digestion", "Circulation", "Reproduction", "Growth"],
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Of the following terms, which one includes all the others",
    answer: "Phylum",
    options: ["Species", "Class", "Phylum", "Order"],
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question:
      "Ciliated epithelial cells in nasal passages are useful because they",
    answer: "Keep out dust and bacteria",
    options: [
      "Keep out dust and bacteria",
      "Provide sense of smell",
      "Reduce the breathing rate when the air is impure",
      "Reduce the humidity in inhaled air",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question:
      "An independent organism is discovered that does not contain a nucleus. In all liklihood, it would be classified in the kingdom",
    answer: "Protista",
    options: ["Monera", "Protista", "Fungi", "Animal"],
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Why do legume plants enrich soil? ",
    answer: "Their roots contain nitrogen-fixing bacteria",
    options: [
      "They remove selenium a deadly poision",
      "They encourage breeding of earthworms",
      "Their roots contain nitrogen-fixing bacteria",
      "Their root system penetrate 2 meter below the surface",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Messanger RNA is important in protein synthesis because it",
    answer: "Carries code from DNA to nucleus",
    options: [
      "Contains the 20 essential amino acids",
      "Carries code from DNA to nucleus",
      "Carries code from DNA to ribosomes",
      "Is transmitted to the nucleotide",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question:
      "In ecological succession, since lichens grow on bare rock, they are considered to be",
    answer: "Pioneer organisms",
    options: [
      "Primary consumers",
      "Pioneer organisms",
      "Climax organisms",
      "Producers",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question:
      "A green plant cell contain all of the following structure except",
    answer: "A centriole",
    options: ["DNA", "Genes", "A cell wall", "A centriole"],
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question:
      "The innermost chamber of respiratory system into which air can be drawn is the",
    answer: "Bronchiole",
    options: ["Bronchiole", "Bronchus", "Air sac", "Bronchiole tube"],
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "In aerobic respiration, the final hydrogen acceptor is",
    answer: "Molecular oxygen",
    options: ["Molecular oxygen", "Carbon dioxide", "Water", "ATP"],
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Antibodies are chemicals that are",
    answer: "Produced by the body in response to antigen",
    options: [
      "Non-specific",
      "Produced by the body in response to antigen",
      "Synthesized from glycogen",
      "Transported by red blood cells",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question:
      "Carbohydrates are organic compounds containing C, H, O in which the hydrogen and oxygen occur in the same ratio as in water. Of the following compounds, the carbohydrate is:",
    answer: "Cellulose (C6H10O5)n",
    options: [
      "Stearin (C57H110O6)",
      "Thiamin (C12H18N4O2S)",
      "Palmatin (C51H98O6)",
      "Cellulose (C6H10O5)n",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "The best description of an enzyme is that it",
    answer: "Speeds up the rate of chemical reactions",
    options: [
      "Becomes hydrolyzed during chemical reactions",
      "Becomes dehydrated during chemical synthesis",
      "Speeds up the rate of chemical reactions",
      "Serves as an inorganic catalyst",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question:
      "A person with insufficient iron in his diet may become anemic because",
    answer: "Iron is used in making hemoglobin",
    options: [
      "The spleen removes too many leucocytes from the blood",
      "The clotting reaction time is reduced",
      "Iron is needed in making fibrinogen",
      "Iron is used in making hemoglobin",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question:
      "What is the main function of Lymphocytes?",
    answer: "Production of Antibodies",
    options: [
      "Production of Antibodies",
      "Production of Antigens",
      "Production of White Blood Cells",
      "All of the above",
    ],
  },
];
